Let's go camping for the first time in Miyagi!
Wow!
This time, we are going to play at Sukekki Aburatsubo Camping Park in Miura Peninsula, Kanagawa Prefecture.
Sukekki Aburatsubo Camp Park in Miura Peninsula, Kanagawa Prefecture!
Wow! Thank you very much!
Today, I have a lot of work to do, like pitching tents, cooking, etc.
We have a lot of work to do!
Yes, that's why we've divided into teams.
Me and Riko are in charge of cooking.
We'll do our best.
And me, Juri and Mai...
What's it called, tent and fire making?
Do you think you can do it?
Don't worry, I have experience making a fire.
It's fun!
Is it?
Yeah, it is.
It's gonna be fun.
Let's do it.
All right, let's have fun taking pictures until the sun goes down.
Okay, I'll get right to it.
Yes, sir!
Okay.
Okay, so this is the cooking team!
Yay!
Yuka is good at cooking, right?
I saw something.
What?
Check the cerebral hematology. Confirmation of cerebral hematology.
Oh, yes confirmation, I heard that the other day.
It was good. It was good.
Yes, I, uh, I posted it to X.
To the X.
So, what are we making? Today.
Yes, today, I'm going to make the camp's famous curry.
Oh my, oh my, oh my.
Are you good at curry, Riko?
Not so bad.
So-so?
Well, well, well. With Yuka, I'd say I'm good at it.
Let's both do our best.
Let's work hard.
Me too. I've never made curry by myself.
Well, then...
With mom.
Me too. Me too.
It's like a show.
Let's do it
Some of the potatoes we got.
Yes, ma'am.
The ones we got first.
We have some.
We have a lot of them.
I'm hoping to make some rice and other things, too.
Okay, I'll do my best!
I'm looking forward to it!
Yes, I'll do my best.
Okay, now, the three of us... Well then, the three of us are going to build a tent now.
I'd like to build a tent.
Yes, sir!
Slowly, the fire... but it's gonna burn.
Just the first hook.
On the first hook.
You want to go for it?
Come on!
Aah!
Let's open it up.
Let's open them all up. Let's take one down.
But, you know, I said, yeah, we did desert island camping.
But, you know, I also built a tent.
And, you know, I started by mowing the lawn.
Oh, you're so serious!
You're so serious!
I mean, when was that?
Four years ago.
Oh?
So I'd appreciate it if you don't think I remember nearly as much as you do now.
Oh, that's a tent!
Oh, wow.
I found something!
I think I can stand it up a little... Oh! Look, look, look!
A manual? There's a manual stuck inside!
Wait, what? What is this? What?
What does that mean? Are you sure? Are you okay?
What is it? Are you sure?
Blue, I can pull it that way. - You can pull it that way.Blue, you can pull it that way.
It's kind of high and... Oh, my gosh!
Is this the right one? No! Does it fit?
I don't know. Wait, is this okay? Are you going to break it?
It's still good, right? I think so.
You're too bright.
Yeah!
Wait, how do I do this?
Is it right here?
It's at an angle.
Right here on the concrete?
Okay, I'll set up the chairs.
Like that.
Topped?
Is it okay?
Should we make it a circle?
Like a semicircle?
There's a camera over here.
Over there.
Julie's yagatsu should be over here.
And then we'll put it in a box, right?
Wait, this is so much fun.
I'm having so much fun.
It's going in.
It won't stop.
I'm not going to stop... it's my sweat that's not going in... it's the state of my mind...
I'm going to cut the kabacha for a good minute!
Oh, no!
If I cut up potatoes, I can make curry anyway. If I cut up potatoes, I can make curry anyway
Cut them up, cut them up, cut them up, cut them up, cut them up, cut them up
Cut them up, cut them up, cut them up, cut them up, cut them up, cut them up, cut them up, cut them up, cut them up, cut them up!
I don't think they're in a pinch, they're just fine to grill.
I'd rather have young corn in my curry or on top of it, but I'm sure there are cute kids out there.
I'd rather put it on top of the curry than on top of it.
I'm sure you're right.
I'll prepare the rice.
I'll prepare the rice...
I don't know how rice is made, but what do you do with it?
I don't know what to do with the rice.
I don't know how to cook rice, but I'll do No. 3 first.
I like porridge, so I don't know if everyone likes porridge.
I like porridge. I wonder if everyone else does too.
I'm sorry about that. I don't care how I cut it.
I might put a little too much in, seriously.
Oh, oh, oh, oh!
I'm the type of person who wants to cook a whole shiitake mushroom...
I'm the type who wants to eat a whole shiitake mushroom, but the person who eats it isn't eating it.
I always do this... but which way is eringi... thinning it out?
I'm in a race against time, and I've got to finish making them by the end of the day.
I've got to finish cooking this until the end of the day...
I'm going to light a fire in the takibi tree to start the fire.
I'll do my best.
I'm sure you'll do great.
You're sure?
Really?
I'll try on my own.
I'll try.
What do I do? I don't know what to do.
I don't burn my hair.
What should I do?
Is it safe to put this in?
I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared.
You want to try it?
Let's try it.
Let's try it together.
I'm scared. I'm scared. I'm scared.
I'm scared.
What do we do?
Wait, wait, wait.
Isn't this... this what you're looking for?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What's it gonna be?
Burn it.
I'm scared, I'm scared, I'm scared.
They're going to burn it.
Juli's hands are gonna burn.
I have a little bit of igniter... that I think I can use.
Oh, God, I'm scared.
Oh, my God, I can see it in my eyes.
What's that? It's not too stiff, is it?
Can you do it? I'm sorry, it's just... it's just... it's bleeding.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey. Are you okay?
I'm sorry, I was wrong.
I'm bringing it over here, so be careful.
Are you lucky? Are you lucky? Are you lucky? Weak. Weak.
Weak. Weak.
Too weak.
Incense. As weak as incense.
Okay, let's see, this one here.
The numbers are wrong.
Let's put this in
Scary, scary, scary.
Scary, scary, scary
Whoa!
It's cute.
Stop it, stop it, stop it. I'm scared.
Aoki is so cute, I can't stop myself from filling it up.
What? Hey, hey, hey... but this...
Hey, hey, hey!
Like this!
I'll put this in too!
It's a big one.
It's a camege!
It's good, it's good, it's good.
That's great, Julie.
Julie, that's nice.
It's kind of fun.
It's a little bit... too much idol power for you, huh?
It's cool.
I want to be like you, Ao.
What do you mean?
No, really. I'm not scared.
You're strong. That's good.It's strong. It's good.
No, it's not.
That's great.
Thinly shaved wood.
That's it! That's it!
That's it!
Oh, my God, Julie, you're so right.
Julie, that's good.
Oh, my God! Oh, man!
Nyajou, active!
Wait, it came suddenly! It came suddenly!
Oh, my God, isn't our sense of humor shining through?
Julie, spit it out, spit it out, spit it out, spit it out!
More vomit? Spit it out, spit it out, spit it out!
Tree, please.
Hey, baby.
You know what's playing in my head right now?
Play a song.
What? What's playing?
It's not what I was promised, but...
Okay, this is it. It's really something. I can't stop thinking about it.
You like to dance, too, don't you?
Are you okay? Are you okay?
Worms? It's like a bee.
I really do live for bugs. Just not bees.
Bees are the worst. I'll go get a bee. It might hurt a little bit.
I think I just got stung on my ankle. There's a lot of bees.
It's in the triangle.
It's tougher than a pumpkin.
This is a new one. This is fresh!
What do you mean, fresh vegetables can be eaten raw?
I wonder if I can eat it.
You'll break your teeth.
Not if they're skinny.
Looks good.
Wow, this is so hard.
Wait, this is my bad.
Oh, I don't have a container to cook onions.
Isn't this thing a beauty?
Ahhh...
Wooo...
Oh, it's a beauty!
Oh, it's a beauty.
Beautiful!
Oh, beautiful!
It's a stage, isn't it?
It's a stage, isn't it, Mirumodopon?
Still lingering?
Seriously, sometimes beautiful girls come down to the stage.
Yeah, I know.
For the six of us.
For the barbecue.
It's done!
This is a freshly-picked sweet potato
It's a sweet potato.
It's absolutely delicious!
I'm sure it will be delicious!
So far, we've worked together.
Wait, wait, look at the color!Wait, wait, wait, look at these colors
The dazzle of snow
Tears can be deceiving
I can cover up my tears
clap clap clap clap clap
ja, ja, ja, ja, ja, ja, ja
Down, down, down
Is it down?
It's good.
You need some of these.
Where?
That's it for the baked sweet potatoes.
Cook some rice.
We'll heat up the curry.
And then we'll barbecue.
That's fine.
It's fine, right?
I've seen that happen.
One more time.
It won't come off.
I can't. I can't. I can't.
Nice.
I'll take this.
It's burning up like crazy.
I'll take that, please.
Chaka-chaka-chaka.
Just so I can put it inside.
It'll be great if you give it to me.It'd be great if we could get it over here.
Are you sure this is the right one?
Omoto.
And these girls are pretty good, too.
This one's probably the best.
I'm scared.
Can you go?
Yeah!
Here we go.
It's coming from the white side, too.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, that sounds good.
Is it hot? Is it okay?
But it's really hot.
Is it burning well?
It's glowing.
Here we go.
Hey, hey, look.
Wow, put it up.
Is that a mountain?
Wow!
That's Mt. Fuji.
You really think all the mountains are Mt. Fuji?
Wait a minute.
I heard that.
It's gone.
That's not good.
Wait, I'm in shock.
My eyes hurt.
If it doesn't ignite, it's gone.If it doesn't ignite, it's gone.
Oh, man.
Dramatic.
This is where it starts.
It already looks delicious!
Absolutely hard
Put the lid on.
Smells good.
It smells good.
I wonder if I should time my enjoyment. Oh, sure, they say you shouldn't open the lid once it starts to beep, even if it's only half an hour or so.
You're not supposed to open it even if it's been beeping for 30 minutes or so.
Wait... then...
Good luck! May it be delicious!
I'm not going to put that much onion in it.
A little bit of onion, a little bit of onion, a little bit of onion, a little bit of onion, a little bit of onion.
Too many carrots, but they're melting.
It's melting. My hair is killing me.
It's good.
It's melting.
Curry's ready.
Ready?
I've got another spatula.
It's hot.
This one's easier.
This is a simple pork curry.
This is pumpkin, eggplant and onion.
A little bit of potato.
I was thinking of putting some grilled vegetables on top.
I'm thinking of putting grilled vegetables on top.
I'm waiting for some green okra or something.Green okra and other things are waiting for us now.
The fire is going strong!
It's not the same as a gas stove, is it?
Is this right?
No water.
Takahashi, the smiling technician. I'm serious.
I'm serious.
I'm watching.
I'll put it in. Good luck.
Oh, that's good.
Don't let it bother you.
That feels good.
Oh, no.
That's good. That's good. That's good.
Mmm. - Mmm.
You're so cute.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on...
I'm going to make a nice baked potato...
I'll make you a nice baked potato...
Good night.
Te oh yes Survivor Boy ......
Chris is precis!
Flash with a little black j!
I'm not here for the sweet potatoes in the morning!
I'm going to put another one in, it's starting to look like a curry.
Mix the roux.
We are the type of people who mix a lot of different roux.
Nice blend!Nice blend.
This time, it's got a little bit of the Murayama family and a little bit of the Fujisawa family.
It's got a little bit of the Murayama family and a little bit of the Fujisawa family in it.
It's all messed up.
Let's see...
There's something about the little ones...
I couldn't divide it into quarters.
Maybe it's not for six.
Maybe it's for six.
That's good. That's good.
It's not boiling this way at all.
Whatever.
It's been a while.
I'm gonna put something tiny in here.
Sounds good.
I want to mix it up.
I'm going to grill some vegetables.
I'm going to put them on top of the curry.
I'll go.
Like a summer vegetable curry.
This is so hot.
I'm so catty.
Be really careful.
It's boiling.
You can keep huffing and puffing.
Is the boiling point okay? This is...
Yum!
We made it!Great success!
Taste it, taste it!
Yummy! It's so good!
It's a success!
Ready!
Ta-da!
It's so beautiful!
It's a little bit oily and a little bit sticky.
Looks delicious.
Wait, that looks good.
Wait, wait, wait.
That looks so good.
Oh, it's good. You want it just like that?
Wow!
Go a little deeper!
That's so good! Can I just, like, break it up a little bit?
Yeah!
Okay, I'm on it.
Okay.
Oh, wait! Oh, my God!
Oh, no!
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
Wait a minute.
Aren't you a genius?
I'm going to go out on a limb here.
Wow! Wait, that looks delicious!
Oh, no!
Wait a minute! Oh, my gosh!
Yum.
A little burnt.A little burnt
Burnt taste good too!
Yum!
Yes!
She's a little carrot-heavy.
I'm sorry if she's a little picky.
There's one who doesn't like it.
Ready, set, go!
Ta-da!
It's done!
In a manner of speaking, there were a lot of grilled vegetables on top of the roux and rice.
and rice, with a lot of grilled vegetables on top.
Colorful!
I made it colorful!
I'm not sure what it tastes like.
There was a curry with pumpkin and eggplant.
and one with carrots, potatoes, and onions.
Each one is made by mixing two kinds of roux.
Yes.
I think it's a unique taste.
Yes, sir.
And the burnt rice, too.
It's so beautiful.
And lots of roasted rice cake, just like in a camp.
It's not golden, but...
But I'm so happy.
It's a beautiful color and it's absolutely delicious.
I hope everyone enjoys it!
Everyone made a lot of food, you know.And a lot of people, too, because you made it.
Yes!
Inomo, Inomo, Inomo...
Inomo-san, Inomo-san, Inomo-san...
All the dishes are ready!
Wow!
Looks delicious!
It smells so good!
No way, let's eat next time.
Let's eat.
Ready?
Bon appétit!
Thank you!
No, we really worked hard for it.
That's great.
Some of these potatoes were taken by the spaceman.
That's right.
The baked sweet potatoes... you guys did an amazing job with the fire.
Can we get on with it now?
Let's eat curry!
Thank you for the curry.
Curry!
There's pickles too.
Oh, that's right.
It's an effort of both of us.
Then, I'll eat it.
Bon appétit!
I'm just curious.I'm curious about ml
Lopez
SQL
едm
Oh, my God!
Boo boo hoo, only one of us didn't make it to the club, it's so good!
I love it when he tells me it's the first time he's had me in a club and I love it so much I'm surprised it's so good.
I'm surprised at how good it tastes I love it I'm surprised at how good it tastes I love it I love it I love it I love it I love it I love it I love it I love it I love it I love it
I'll bake the keys, too... and I'll eat them with Pico.
I want to play a game with the superhero Roy, I want to break the smallest of the small.
How are the pictures?
I'd like to play a game with the super-small boys.
Yeah, we're... we're... we're... we're... we're... we're... we're...
It's expensive now.
Every time I eat a meal, I get more and more ingredients.
I'm sure you'd like his baby more than anything else you've ever had in your life.
I'll cry if I have to.
I'm going to have a barbecue now, and I've been told I have to have a lot of food, so I bought a lot of food, and I was grilling a lot.
I bought a lot of food, so I'm going to barbecue a lot.
I'm going for the beef tongue... which looks delicious, but I don't like it either.
I'm going for the beef tongue.
Shrimp looks so good... let's do it!
I'm off then, Tombu.
Oh, it's so quiet, but I can hear you inside.
I don't know about the oil or the rice, but I'm going to make a line of them for 5 minutes in the sandwiches.
I don't know what it is, but I'll line it up five minutes down the road.
I'm going to go and do a kilo-computer, my car.
I don't know if it's the best part of camping or what, but... the two of you cooked this for him, and he... this is...
He made it for me because he wanted it so bad. He made it and he wanted it so bad, so he wanted it so bad, so he wanted it so bad.
More channel saiccups than ever after... blue sea!
The vegetables are not cooked too well.
I can feel the sun coming up soon, right?
But the texture's still there.
What do you want to do when you're 19?
I mean, you're a kid, you're in your 50s, you're a kid.
I mean, you start drinking when you're 20, and you start getting the wind up, right?
But I became an adult at 18, so there's nothing I can't do.
But it's the last time I'm a teenager.
I'm glad I got this kind of job in my teenage years.
I auditioned when I was about 17.
That's probably right.
Around 17?
Yeah, 17.
Then when you turned 18.
That's right. I was in the final round.
It's been...
It's been amazing every day.
That's right.
It's a fast-paced life.
I'm so thankful.
I'm 17 years old.
I wanted to join this group.
It's been almost two years.
The audition has just started, right? It takes about an hour or two.
Two years is fast, isn't it?
It's gone by so fast.
We've been going out for dinner as the oldest group, but we haven't been able to go, right?
Yeah, the four of us.Yes, the four of us.
We promised that when we turn 20, we'd all have a drink together.
That's what we're doing.
We are.
We are. There are four of us.
That makes me happy.
And they're all different shapes and sizes. Yes, yes, yes.
So we can all rely on each other.
Riko is calm.
And her mind is very dependable.
Like, "It's okay, it's okay. It's okay.
Miyuka corrects me.
That's true.
I guess I'm just thinking this way.
Thank you so much.
But you know what, Ai does the right thing too.
But Yuka and Aimi are different.
It's different, isn't it? What I don't have, Ai has.
It's hard to put into words.
Aimi really makes me feel like a great big sister.
That's true.
Isn't she your type?
I don't think I know her that well.
That's true.
Ayumi is really mature.
Ayumi's the kind of person who can give a third-party opinion from the vantage point of a flag.
She gives us a bird's eye view.
When we are thinking like this, we are just looking forward to the next event.
Ayumi is the one who gives us the most objective opinion when we are only looking forward.
That's true.That's true.
So, you know, it's like, you know, it's like, you know, it makes sense.
You put it all together.
It's just how I feel at the time.
I want to hear her opinion. I want to hear her real opinion.
Yeah, the older ones are really reliable.
Am I... am I talking right?
Are you okay? You and me, at night.
The furthest part of the dinner.
We're kind of talking about the ocean back there.
Let's go to bed.
Let's go to bed. I really want to go.
You're going home today? Tokyo.
I don't want to go back.
I don't want to.
No, no, no.
Look at this.
It looks so good!
The meat smells so good. It's done.
It's a piece of beef tongue and a piece of beef for roasting.
Looks delicious.
As if the shine is exquisite.
One bite
Looks so delicious!
Beautiful.
Tasty?
Your eyes are shining.
This is the best barbecue meat I've ever tasted.
Do you know why?
Why?Why?
They all have exquisite voices.
Miku!
It's the same guys from the stage!
Miku the 2nd!
So many nets! So many beautiful contacts!
I'm just going to eat more and more!
Yes!
Yes, that's what I'm talking about.
Normally, I would have bought fireworks.
I'd like to have fireworks with everyone!
Wow!
That's great.
We did it! Summer's over and I'm still
I'm so happy!
Yay!
Wow!
Beautiful!
Wait.
Oh!
No fire.
Yay!
Account to collar
Man Bol
Bol
BolBol
Seino
Oh, here we are!
Wait, this ran out in a second.
Wait, I lost it in seconds.Wait, I lost it in seconds.
No way.
You're still here.
Wait, I smell fireworks.
Summer.
Oh, no.
Oh, wait.
What?
My hand.
No, no, no, it's not too late.
I'm not done yet.
I can still do it.
I'm here.
Wait for me!
8 Kokça... but... we went around the same thing.
Right?
ah ah ah ah ah ah ah
ass aai wood 4
cars asphalt
It's over!
Active
Active, isn't it?
Active, so active fighting part 2!
I'll be waiting for it!
It was fun!
If you like this video
If you like this video, please subscribe to our channel, click the "Good" button, and leave a comment!
That's all for now.
That's all for now.It was Nyarikozu-chan!
Bye bye!
Please subscribe to our channel!